# Muhammad Ilham Haqqi

Central Java. Indonesia



ilhamserbaguna@gmail.com



linkedin.com/in/hagger

# Summary

Experienced Information Technology Support Technician with a demonstrated history of working in the government administration industry. Skilled in Python and Javascript, Web Applications, RESTful WebServices, and REST API. Strong information technology professional graduated from Universitas Dian Nuswantoro.

## **Experience**

## Software Engineer

Azura Labs

Oct 2021 - Present (1 year 9 months)

# IT Support Technician

Dinas Penataan Ruang Kota Semarang

Mar 2019 - Present (4 years 4 months)

Created Distaru API Service, integrating DISTARU AP Service with Bappenda Payment gateway

# Software Engineer

Azura Labs

Sep 2019 - Oct 2021 (2 years 2 months)

work mostly as Backend Engineer, working with Golang and gRPC also with NodeJS

# **FLS** Full Stack Developer

**Future Leader Summit** 

Apr 2019 - Sep 2019 (6 months)

Develop App registration and Organization, also prepare and setup web service

#### **Education**



#### 📵 Universitas Dian Nuswantoro

Teknologi Informasi 2017 - 2023

## Skills

Web Development • Web Services • Web Applications • JavaScript • RESTful WebServices • REST APIs • Linux • Network Engineering • Docker • Node.js